Hi everyone! Welcome to a new video. I'm Celine and today I'm going to show you
more roleplay lingerie outfits from Bad Stories. I have several sets here from
the new Halloween collection and the mystery collection and I think they're
called Freemason Girl, Kitty Pop and Gothic Lady. Bad Stories is a Ukrainian
brand and as you can see the boxes are already really nice and now I'm going to
open them with one hand. It's not that easy. When I opened the box for the first time I
saw this cute little bag and I was surprised because it has my name on here
which is really cute. Opening the bag I have to find the first outfit and I'm going to
change. Straight from the mystery collection this is the outfit called
gothic lady and it consists of the bra the skirt garter belt and a blindfold
I'm going to show you in a second I put some stockings on because this is a
garter belt but I think I would name it a skirt because it's really long and it
gives you this kind of dressed look because of course it's only bra and top
part but there's a lot of fabric going on which is see-through all the way.
That's why I'm wearing undies. And I love the different combination of fabrics
like the sheer mesh and the one with the pattern here with the teeny tiny dots
everywhere which you can also find in the bra here and in this collar part here
because this bra collar thing is one piece so everything together. And I love
the shape of it. You have like corset boning here underneath so there's this arc here and then this
I don't know how to call it zigzag crisscross pattern with straps here and this collar part.
I just think it's a really really cute design and a really cute outfit all together.
As I just mentioned there is the two line fold included also with the same fabric again
although there is a nude fabric behind it.
So it's not just one layer but two which gives it a firmer look or feel.
But I have to see how I match with the fake lashes on.
So the blindfold.
It's rather comfortable because it's not too tight on face.
So it's just a headband here.
And I think it gives kind of a completion to the look.
So it ties everything together from the stockings to the hat.
So it is see-through due to the holes in the fabric and the nude mesh fabric behind that.
Just my tip, do not wear lashes that are too long, otherwise you'll have problems opening your eyes
and closing them because the lashes will move against the fabric. Next up is something new
from Bad Stories and a bodysuit or rather catsuit, so I'm really curious.
Yeah, it has ears. Cat ears. It's the Kitty Pop catsuit from the new Halloween collection.
And I think there's also a mouse and a bunny. So you should check it out. I'll link everything
in the description text of course. And I'm going to turn around first. Oh, there's still
the tab so it's brand new first try on and I have to say it fits really good
there are two different lengths for this item which is amazing because I of
course chose the taller version the longer version and it fits super good
here in the body part so perfect bed stories thumbs up for offering two
different lengths options here. It's basically a transformer catsuit. A cat
suit. Get it? Because you can also detach the legs and then you have like a short
clay suit or the full length bodysuit and I love that the leg is flared so it
gives off like a party vibe immediately and also it's really long the legs are super long so
wearing shoes and heels beneath it is no problem
looks really cool definitely my favorite so far also with cat ears of course and i think i'm going
to detach the legs so we can have a look at that option.
And here go the legs.
This is a super cool, I'm just going to put it in here, a super cool feature.
Because now you have two looks.
Let me check the mirror.
I think both are really unique like this kind of place you with a really short leg it's really
cute also I love that the metal rings are still attached to the short version so it matches the
zipper of course you could act like a silver choker or yeah chain to your neck here to complete the
outfit. I like the long version better because it keeps me warm. Average or practical. I don't know,
but I also like this one. It's really cute. I love the whole design. Also with the long flared legs
and I'm just a fan of this, okay? But let's do the next one. The third outfit, the Freemanson Lady
and oh, going to get rid of the cat ears sadly. They might look cute as well.
Yeah, goodbye cat ears. So I had to improvise a bit with this outfit because it's really
not much. So I put a nude bra underneath and put a robe I had at home on top.
Actually there is a matching Freemanson lady robe from Bad Stories. Sadly it didn't
arrive in time for this video so I used one I had at home. The one from Bad Stories
is way cooler, it has a big hood and looks way better. But all for the YouTube safety
here because you know YouTube police I can hear them again.
I'm going to get rid of the belt.
So you can see a bit more of the outfit.
It's a panty and a bra.
I'm going to call it a bra, although it's...
I don't know if it classifies as a bra, if there's no fabric here.
and you have the Bed Story logo here in the eye which is a really cute touch.
I'm wearing the pasties on top of my bra here but like I said this is just the improvised version.
If you're not wearing a new bra underneath then just wear the pasties or I don't know nothing at
depending on where you're going. About the G or the pennies I had a look and I did my research.
It stands for Geo... Geo... Geometry because of the Freemasons and their
mathematic approach. Yeah so that's what I found out. I hope it's true. So any Freemasons here
it's your time to shine in the comments down below. If you like the outfits I showed you,
Kittypop, Gothic Lady and Freemason Lady.
That story just started a halfway to Halloween sale and you can get the three
outfits I showed you for 20% off until November 1st. Just have a look in the
description text. I said I have three outfits. I showed you three outfits but I
have another outfit I'm going to show you if you're like not into all black
outfits or if you like capes so check it out this is the super lady from a
previous collection and I showed it before in a video along with a lot of
other outfits so if you want to see them you can click here and check the outfit
out I just thought I'm going to bring a bit of color into this video for the end
because now I'm done and that was everything for today I hope you had fun
with this video tell me your favorite outfit in the comments I'm still going
with the kitty pop catsuit and see you in the next video thanks to bad stories
also bye have a nice day